greatrivermilling.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy Policy | Organic agriculture, sustainable agriculture, stone-ground flour. Kosher approved grains. | Fountain, City, WI

At Great River Organic Milling, your privacy is of utmost importance to us. While information comprises the foundation of our ability to provide superior service, the trust of our customers is held in the highest of regards. We DO NOT share or sell information that we gather to any company, organization,    or person outside of our organization. 

Information Collection 

Great River Organic Milling is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site. Great River Organic Milling collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. The information (name, address,phone number, email address, and business characteristics) entered by individuals or businesses that subscribe to our site is maintained in our server database. The email addresses of those who subscribe are stored in a database that is used only to communicate new offers, specials, and information to the subscribers. 

To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small text files, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a web site to "personalize" itself for each user. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service, customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. No third party has access to the information we collect this way, but if you’d rather we didn't use cookies when you visit us, you can set your browser not to accept cookies. If you do disable cookies in your browser, you may not be able to take advantage of certain personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our web site. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

Great River Organic Milling will not share or sell any personally identifiable information we gather to any company, organization, or person outside of the organization. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses, we will post the policy changes to our web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. 

Security 

Information transmissions over the Internet cannot be 100% secure. However, Great River Organic Milling places a high priority on security and privacy by limiting access to our site to only authorized users who have valid passwords. In addition, Great River Organic Milling maintains a firewall to protect database from third parties. Great River Organic Milling takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. Great River Organic Milling employees are made aware of our security policies and practices. We periodically review security policies and practices so that updates may be made as necessary in order to ensure the protection of visitor information obtained via our web site.

Updating and Deleting Personal Information 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail to [info@greatrivermilling.com](mailto:info@greatrivermilling.com), calling us at the below telephone number, or writing to us at the below address. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by e-mailing us at [info@greatrivermilling.com](mailto:info@greatrivermilling.com), or writing to us at the below address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at [info@greatrivermilling.com](mailto:info@greatrivermilling.com), calling us at the below telephone number, or writing to us at the below address. Please provide us with your name and phone number. 

Links 

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Great River Organic Milling is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

Contact Information 

Great River Organic Milling reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you have any other questions, concerns or comments, you may contact us at the below addresses or telephone number. 

Postal Address:  
Great River Organic Milling   
P.O. Box 185   
Fountain City, WI 54629 

Corporate Office:   
Great River Organic Milling   
118 South Main Street   
Fountain City, WI 54629 

Online Orders: 

Orders can be placed using Paypal. We accept Mastercard, Visa, and Discover. We do not store any credit card information. Your credit card is charged when your order ships. Orders made with your credit card will appear on your credit card statement as “Great River Organic Milling.” 

Telephone Orders: 

Call (507) 457-0334 to place your order by telephone. Our office hours are 8am – 4pm CST, Monday thru Friday. If you reach our customer service messaging, please leave your name and phone number and we will return your call promptly. 

Mail Orders: 

Contact us for an order form. Be sure to complete fully and sign your order form. 

Postal Address:   
Great River Organic Milling   
P.O. Box 185   
Fountain City, WI 54629 

We will accept checks or money orders. 

Shipping 

In most cases we will ship USPS. Alaska, Hawaii and P.O. Boxes  additional fees may apply. Please allow 5-7 days for delivery. Great River Organic Milling reserves the right to choose alternate carriers for delivery as needed. 

Returns 

We want you to be satisfied with your purchase. If you are not satisfied with the merchandise you purchased from our site, you can return the merchandise within 20 days from the day received and we will refund your money excluding the shipping fee. Items may be returned as long as it is in the original packaging and condition. 

Refunds will be credited to the same credit card as the original purchase. A refund check will be sent for orders paid by personal check or money order. Packages received after the 20 day time period are subject to a restocking fee or return back to you. 

We ship each order with care and special attention but, on occasion, orders are damaged in transit or packed incorrectly. If your order is damaged or incorrect when your receive it, please keep all the original boxes and packaging material. Damaged items or items with missing or damaged parts must be reported within 7 days of delivery. 

Terms of Use 

Great River Organic Milling expressly reserves all intellectual property rights in all text, programs, products, processes, technology, content and other materials which appear on this Site. 

The Great River Organic Milling name and logos, and all related products and service names, design marks, and slogans are the trademarks, service marks or registered trademarks of Great River Organic Milling. 

All other product, trademarks and service marks contained herein are the property of their respective owners. Great River Organic Milling does not assume any legal liability or responsibility for any product or process purchased at Great River Organic Milling. In no event shall Great River Organic Milling be liable for any special, indirect, or consequential damage or any damages whatsoever arising out of or in connection with the use of Great River Organic Milling.
